[
  {
    "id": "q100",
    "question": "In bad weather, many drivers tailgate large vehicles. What should you do?",
    "choices": [
      "Increase your following distance.",
      "Lightly tap your brake to warn the tailgater to drop back.",
      "Speed up to distance yourself from the tailgater."
    ],
    "answerIndex": 0
  },
  {
    "id": "q99",
    "question": "Most skids:",
    "choices": [
      "Happen on ice.",
      "Do not happen with radial tires.",
      "Are caused by going too fast or trying to stop too quickly."
    ],
    "answerIndex": 2
  },
  {
    "id": "q98",
    "question": "Which of the following is NOT a characteristic of tire failure?",
    "choices": [
      "Cold steering.",
      "Vehicle's fishtail.",
      "Steering wheel twisting."
    ],
    "answerIndex": 0
  },
  {
    "id": "q97",
    "question": "Sometimes you need to leave a road to avoid a hazard or emergency. When you do, you should keep in mind that:",
    "choices": [
      "Most shoulders are not strong enough to support a heavy vehicle.",
      "You might be unable to re-enter the road because of the gravel used on shoulders.",
      "It is less dangerous to drive onto the shoulder than to cause a collision."
    ],
    "answerIndex": 1
  },
  {
    "id": "q96",
    "question": "Stab braking should not be used on vehicles with:",
    "choices": [
      "Anti-lock brakes.",
      "Trailers.",
      "Hazardous materials."
    ],
    "answerIndex": 0
  },
  {
    "id": "q95",
    "question": "You must stop on a hill or curve on a two-lane, two-way road. How far should you place reflective triangles?",
    "choices": [
      "Within 200 feet behind you.",
      "As far back as necessary so others can see you.",
      "Within 500 feet behind you."
    ],
    "answerIndex": 2
  },
  {
    "id": "q94",
    "question": "When you are parked on the side of the road at night, you must:",
    "choices": [
      "Turn on your four-way emergency flashers to warn others.",
      "Use your taillights to give warning to other drivers.",
      "Put out your emergency warning lights within 30 minutes."
    ],
    "answerIndex": 0
  },
  {
    "id": "q93",
    "question": "Backing of the commercial vehicle is:",
    "choices": [
      "Not dangerous if you don't have to turn.",
      "Always dangerous.",
      "Not dangerous if you have a helper."
    ],
    "answerIndex": 1
  },
  {
    "id": "q92",
    "question": "When driving through the work zone, you should:",
    "choices": [
      "Turn on your parking lights.",
      "Watch for sharp pavement drop off.",
      "Reduce your speed only if workers are close to the roadway."
    ],
    "answerIndex": 1
  },
  {
    "id": "q91",
    "question": "When driving at night, you should use your high beams when oncoming traffic is not within ____ feet?",
    "choices": [
      "400",
      "300",
      "500"
    ],
    "answerIndex": 0
  }
]
